thegainsboroughbathspa.co.uk 2013-11-27

# The Gainsborough Bath Spa

**Our commitment to your privacy**  
YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd understand that your privacy is important and will ensure as far as possible that personal information collected through this website is used only for the purposes set out in this Privacy Statement.

**Introduction**  
This Privacy Statement explains the policies of YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd in relation to the handling of personal information that may be collected on this website.

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of personal information by YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd as set out in this Privacy Statement. 

**Children**  
As we cannot distinguish the age of persons who access our website, a blanket privacy policy is applied. If a child has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should email us to remove the information and unsubscribe them from any promotional contact opportunities. YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd does not intend to nor does it seek to receive information from minors. 

**Information collected**  
We collect the following types of information from you: 

| 1 | General statistical information about visitors to our website for general reporting and to improve future content. Such information includes service provider, browser type, pages accessed on our website and what site you came from;  
---|---  
2 | Personal information about you to provide you with a range of personalised services. The type of personal information we collect about you depends on how you use the website; and  
3 | Records of any Emails or other communication or correspondence that you send via this website.  
  
You have full control whether or not to disclose any personal information we may request and the type of information or communication (if any) you would like to receive from our companies or our respective related and associated companies or corporations. 

Generally, you can visit most parts of this website without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Please note, however, that some services offered on our website are not accessible unless the required personal information is supplied. 

**Opting out**  
You will occasionally receive emails from our company and our respective related and associated companies or corporations about special offers, new products or services and other noteworthy news items. We hope you will find this information and updates interesting and informative. 

Please note that we will only send email promotions or announcements to you if you have previously given your permission for us to do so. The Registration Form includes a check box where you can indicate your email promotion and announcement permission preference. 

If you would like to change your permission preference after registering for any of our contests or to unsubscribe from receiving our mailings or do not want us to share your email address with other parties, please contact us. 

You can also automatically [Unsubscribe](http://promotions.ytlhotels.com/webagent/Unsubscribe.aspx) any time from any emails or e-newsletters you receive after registering through this website. 

**Usage of personal information by YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd **  
You agree that YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd may use and disclose the personal information you provide through this website as follows: 

1 | For the purposes for which the personal information was requested;  
---|---  
2 | For use in the marketing of other products and services by YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd;  
3 | To disclose your personal information to relevant authorities when required to by or under law or regulation, or directive of any regulatory authority/body or court order of any jurisdiction;  
4 | We will not sell your name or other private profile information to third parties, and do not intend to do so in the future.  
  
**Security**  
YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd will take reasonable steps to protect the personal information you share with us. We have implemented technology and security features in line with reasonable industry standard practices to safeguard the privacy of your personal identifiable information. 

In addition, if you become aware of any security breach, please let us know as soon as possible. 

Please do not share any of your personal information, such as passwords or personal identification numbers, with anyone. Your assistance will help us protect the privacy of your personal information. Please note that if you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to other legal consequences. In any event, you are solely responsible for keeping your User ID and password. 

YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd cannot be held responsible or liable in any manner for lapses in security caused by third-party accesses to your personal information supplied to us as a result of your failure to keep your personal information private. 

However, you acknowledge and agree that no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, notwithstanding any contrary provisions herein, expressed or implied, whilst we, namely YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd, will reasonably strive to protect your personal information as aforesaid, none of us can ensure or warrant the security of any information you share with or furnish or transmit to us. As such you agree that all disclosure of your personal information to us is at your own risk, and none of us shall be responsible or liable in any manner to you or any other person for any loss, injury, damage, expenses, demands, claims, actions and/or proceedings incurred, suffered or sustained as a consequence thereof. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small file of information that a website transfers to your PC for identification purposes. 

This website uses cookies to authenticate registered visitors. These cookies contain no personal information and are temporary. 

They are automatically deleted after twenty minutes of inactivity on this website or as soon as you close your browser, whichever occurs first. 

**Access to information**  
Where practicable, you may obtain a copy of the personal information collected about you on this website upon written request and payment of a reasonable fee determined by YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd. Please send your request via Contact. 

**Links to other Sites**  
This site may contain links to other websites. YTL Hotels & Properties Sdn Bhd shall not be responsible or liable to you or any other person in any manner for any other websites including their respective privacy policies, practices and content. 

**Changes to the Privacy Statement**  
We may amend this Privacy Statement from time to time and notify you by posting the amended version on this website. 

**Contact information**  
If you have comments or questions about this Privacy Statement, please contact us.
